nortonpro.com 2016-01-20

# Norton Security Backup – Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting NortonSecurityBackup.com (hereinafter referred to as “the Site”) and reviewing our Privacy Policy, effective April 2, 2012. Please read the following policy to understand how personal information that you provide through the Site will be collected and used. Please note that we review our privacy practices from time to time, and that our practices are subject to change. We ask that you bookmark and periodically review this page to ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our Privacy Policy. All amended terms shall be automatically effective after they are posted on the Site. Your use of this Site after any such changes have been posted constitutes your agreement to those changes.

By visiting the Site, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use or access the Site.

This Site is not intended for visitors that are under eighteen (18) years of age. We do not knowingly solicit or collect information from individuals under the age of eighteen (18) years old.

**What Personally Identifiable Information does the Site collect?**  
The Site collects information when you complete and submit any form or otherwise transmit any information to us through your access to and use of the Site. This information may include, without limitation, your name, email address and whether you wish to join our mailing list. Additionally, we save browsing and data log information linked to your usage of the Site. This information may be linked to personally identifiable information we have collected about you.

**What are “cookies” and how does the Site use them?**  
The Site may use data collection devices such as “cookies” to store, and sometimes track, information about you and your browsing experience through the Site. A cookie is a small file containing a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and placed on your computer’s hard drive to assist us in providing our services. All pages on the Site where you are prompted to login or that are customizable may require that you accept cookies. Our cookies are only read by the server that placed them and are unable to execute any code or virus. 

More specifically, we may use cookies to:  
(1) Remind us of who you are when you access your account information and/or use the service in order to deliver to you a more personalized service;  
(2) Measure your visiting patterns in the aggregate. Aggregate data (data gathered across all user accounts) may be gathered in a non-personally identifiable form to build higher quality online services by performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our visitors, such as how long and how often users view certain pages;  
(3) Determine your clickstream to the Site;  
(4) Better personalize the content that you and other users will see on the Site;  
(5) Collect IP addresses and log-in information for system administration;  
(6) Automatically share some information with Google Analytics and/or other analytics programs to analyze a broad range of information. However, the analytics are exclusively for our internal use to better manage the website experience for our visitors and evaluate advertising strategies and tactics; and  
(7) Other purposes to assist us in delivering the highest quality service possible. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits. 

**How does the Site use my information?**  
The Site uses your information to provide you the products or services you requested as well as other communications from trynortonantivirus.com, such as transactional and promotional email communications. We also may use your personal information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, respond to your inquiries, detect and protect against error, fraud, or other criminal activity, enforce our Terms of Use, and for any other such purposes that we deem appropriate.

This Site may display the advertisements and/or links to Norton Antivirus and/or other independent third parties (“advertisers”). We do not provide your personally identifiable information to those advertisers. However, if you independently interact with those advertisers after using our Site, those advertisers may collect personally identifiable information about you subject to the terms of their own privacy policies, which you should review.

**With whom does the Site share my information?**  
In addition to any other information sharing or disclosure practices described in this Privacy Policy, we may share your personal and non-personal information with third party contractors or service providers who assist us with the preparation and mailing of our business and marketing communications, and with order processing and fulfillment functions. For example, we may disclose your email address to email fulfillment contractors to send you emails from us. 

We may share some or all of your personal information with our subsidiaries and affiliates, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, “affiliates”), in which case we will require these affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. If our Company or our assets are acquired by another company, that company will possess the personal information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or to comply with valid legal process (such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order), to protect the company’s rights or property (including without limitation in the event of a transfer of control of company or substantially all of its assets), or during emergencies when safety is at risk. 

**What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?**  
Whenever the Site handles your personal information, we take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with the relevant Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy. Your information is stored on our servers located in the United States. We use procedural and mechanical safeguards to protect your personal information against loss or theft as well as unauthorized access and disclosure to protect your privacy, including encryption. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We cannot, therefore, warrant or ensure the security if any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

If you choose to share your personal information with Norton Antivirus and/or other third parties, you are responsible for all actions they take with your personal information, and therefore you should review that third party’s privacy policy.

**Additional Information**  
This Policy and the relevant Terms of Use are the sole authorized statements of NortonSecurityBackup.com’s practices with respect to the online collection of personally identifiable information and the usage of such information. Any summaries of this Privacy Policy generated by third party software or otherwise shall have no legal effect, are in no way binding upon NortonSecurityBackup.com, shall not be relied upon in substitute for this Privacy Policy, and neither supersede nor modify this Privacy Policy.
